{
    "question": "Buatlah 1 contoh recount text",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "last holiday i went to my grandparents house. me and my family went to a mall",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "there-care-many-reasons-for-keeping-dogs-as-pete-in-the-city-area-554",
            "question": "There care many reasons for keeping dogs as Pete in the city area, but many peo- ple feel that keeping pet dogs should not be allowed In the city. Dogs are often not taken care properly. They are kept in small backyards and rarely taken for walks. They are left in the yard all day by themselves while the family rune work. Very little attention is given to the dog and it is not a very good life for it. It is no wonder why these dogs bark and disturb the neighbours and become a nuisance to the community.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 On the other hand, not all people treat their dogs this may and why should the peo- ple receive a lot of pleasure and enjoyment from dog's stifle'? Dogs can make a lonely person's life happy or make wonderful play- mate. It can also teach a child responsibility as they not only Potts lay with the dog, but also need to exercise, feed, and care for the dog.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 I feel that we should be allowed to keep dogs in the city, because ills is taken care of properly, dogs can be a great source of pleasure. As a child / used to enjoy playing and taking care of my pet. There is not greater loyalty a nelson can get than from a well-caned dog.\u00a0    1. Some people do not like the presence of pet dogs In their surroundings because ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) the dogs are left in the yards\u00a0 \r\n(B) the dogs are often neglected \r\n(C) the dogs often bark and disturb the neighbours \r\n(D) the dogs play with the owner's child \r\n(E) the dogs guard the security of the enyit onrnent\u00a0 \r\n\r\n2. The main idea of the last paragraph is ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) pet dogs are loyal animals \r\n(B) pet dogs are more loyal than humans \r\n(C) dogs can be a great source of pleasure \r\n(D) the writer has no objection to keeping dogs In the city \r\n(E) the writer used to play and took care of his pet when he was a child\u00a0 \r\n\r\n3. We can infer from the text that keeping pet dogs in the city will not cause any problem as long ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) the dogs are amusing \r\n(B) the neighbours like having pet dogs \r\n(C) the dogs do not balk at the neighbours \r\n(D) the writer has succeeded in persuading the neighbours \r\n(E) its presence does not disturb the neighbourhood",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1.c.the dogs often bark and disturb the neighbours<br>2.c.dogs can be a great source of pleasure<br>3.e.it&#039;s presence does not disturb the neighbourhood<br>ini menurut jawaban saya :)",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-percakapan-expression-care-826",
            "question": "Contoh percakapan expression care",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "how poor you are<br>what a pity<br>i am sorry to hear that",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Situation : Your friend is sad.<br><br>Ana : <strong>Are you okay? You look so sad.</strong><br>Nia : <em>No, I&#039;m not okay.</em> I feel so sad because I had a fight with my brother yesterday.<br>Ana : Why?<br>Nia : He took my favorite novel without asking my permission and he ripped it! How can I not sad? He even not sorry at all and when I yelled at him, he yelled me back with his ridiculous reason that why should I got sad over a novel!<br>Ana : You must be really hurt...<br>Nia : Of couse I do.<br>Ana : <strong>What should I do to cheer you up?</strong><br>Nia : <em>Thanks for your attention</em> but no, sorry.<br>Ana : <strong>Really?</strong> I&#039;m sorry I can&#039;t help you much.<br>Nia: <em>Yeah, thanks</em>.<br><br><strong>bold: expressions<br></strong><em>italic: responses</em><strong><br></strong>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bantuin-aku-dong-cari-biografi-aknes-monica-menggunakan-bahasa-in-292",
            "question": "Bantuin aku dong cari Biografi aknes monica menggunakan Bahasa inggris",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Agnes Monica Muljoto. Born in Jakarta 1 July 1986, known abroad as Agnes Mo. She stared her career in the entertainment industry at the age of six as a child singer. She jobs is singer, actress, dancer, voice actress, and producer.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-buatkan-teks-bahasa-inggris-tentang-pengalaman-yang-terd-803",
            "question": "Tolong buatkan teks bahasa inggris (tentang pengalaman) yang terdapat Simple Past Tense dan Simple Perfect Tense!!",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<strong>NEW YEARS HOLIDAY<br></strong>When my holiday at home alone, do not go anywhere, when New Years, i was my large family grilled chicken. Very happy family get together, but this year&#039;s holiday was not very pleasent, for some reason??but with family better from with my friend, at the same moment, i stay at home or help my mom. This holiday very boring, calm only, not go play, my mom a sick, this holiday only talk my mom.<strong><br></strong>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Last week, me and my friends went on a road trip to Bali. We rented a jeep, and travel around, through mountains until beaches. We went to\u00a0Mount Agung, it\u00a0would be cold and foggy, but we&#039;ll also see the beauty of the island from up there. Next, we went down and reach a beach called the Pink Beach. By there, we go on boats to see smaller islands, which was fun. We traveled around Bali for 2 weeks, and it was fun.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bantu-nyusun-kata-kata-ne-jadi-klimat-yg-bner-ya-yang-dimulai-dri-452",
            "question": "Bantu nyusun kata-kata ne jadi klimat yg bner ya yang dimulai dri yg bergaris bawah sama bantu buatkan CONDITIONAL SENTENCE TIPE 2    arrange the jumbled words to form meaningful sentences,starting with the underlined words.\r\n1. phone-puppet-his-invite-the-I-number-my-see-Finto-know-will-if-show-to-I-at-place\r\n2. and-holiday-Bali-if-have-will-his-Lombok-long-go-year-Mr. Kukuh-family-to-they-and-this-a\u00a0mohon di bantu",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. If\u00a0 I know his phone number, I will invite Finto to the puppet show at my place.<br>2. If Mr. Kukuh and his family go to Bali, they will have a long holiday to Lombok this year.<br>Sorry kalau salah, baru pemula hehehe<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-percakapan-making-and-handling-cancellation-gimana-ya-ada-918",
            "question": "Contoh percakapan making and handling cancellation gimana ya?\r\nada yang bisa bantu",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "David : Excuse me. I think there is a mistake in our bill. We didn&#039;t have dinner here lst night.<br>Receptionist : I&#039;m sorry, sir. Here&#039;s the bill from the hotel restaurant. It&#039;s got your signature on it.<br>David : But that&#039;s not my signature. I&#039;d like to speak to the manager.<br>Receptionist : I&#039;m sorry, sir. The manager is busy.<br>Manager : You have a complaint about your bill, sir ?<br>David : Yes. I&#039;m afraid there&#039;s a mistake. We didn&#039;t have dinner in the restaurant last night.<br>Manager : But this looks like your signature on the restaurant bill.<br>Let me see. Oh dear I&#039;m very sorry. There&#039;s another couple called Morris in the hotel.<br>They had dinner last night. Not you. I do apologize.<br><br>sudah ya cukup :)\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buatlah-contoh-pecakapan-bahasa-inggris-tentang-pemesanan-meja-di-618",
            "question": "Buatlah contoh pecakapan bahasa inggris tentang pemesanan meja di restoran..",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "A: i want to ask permission<br>B: yes of course<br>A: two days there will be an event in my home, can i order 2 pieces of table<br>B: of course may be happy<br>A: ok i&#039;ll wait for tomorrow<br>B: okay, thank you&#039;ve booked a table here<br>A: you&#039;re welcome<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<span>A: Good afternoon <br>b: Good afternoon, can I help you? <br>A: I would like to reserve a table, for tomorrow afternoon? <br>b: yes, it could. for how many people? <br>A: I would like to reserve a table for lunch two people! <br>B: Yes sir, tomorrow daytime table number five <br>A: Thank you<span>.</span></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "combine-the-sentences-using-too-so-or-either-and-neither-1-d-745",
            "question": "Combine the sentences using : Too, so, or either and neither    1. Dogs\u00a0can't eat vegetables. Cats can't eat vegetables\r\n2. We haven't eaten yet. Father hasn't yet\r\n3. Mitha is not seventeen years old. I am not seventeen years old\r\n\r\nJawabannya yang Jelas ya :)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. Dogs can&#039;t eat vegetables. Neither can cats<br>2. We haven&#039;t eaten yet. Father hasn&#039;t either<br>3. Mitha is not seventeen years old. I am not either<br><br>setau aku begitu aja sih udah betul. mudah-mudahan membantu ya:)",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-kalimat-past-tense-menggunakan-used-to-712",
            "question": "Contoh kalimat past tense menggunakan used to",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "that scissors used my mom<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "contohnya : i used to studying at night<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-buatin-dialog-expresing-anger-untuk-2-orang-524",
            "question": "Tolong buatin dialog expresing anger :)\r\nuntuk 2 orang",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Everyone Has Bad Day<br>Sari\t: Hey, Rangga!<br> Rangga\t: What displeasure!<br> Sari\t: What? What happened, Rangga? Are you angry about something?<br> Rangga\t: Oh, I\u2019m very sorry, Sari. I was walking near handkerchief. You can wipe up your wet shirt.<br>Rangga\t: Oh, thank you, Sari. So, how was your day, Sari? Did something bad happen to you too? Haha I\u2019m kidding, Sari.<br> Sari\t: Actually, something bad did happen to me. It\u2019s still driving me mad until now.<br> Rangga\t: Oh, really? What do you look so insulted about?<br>\n Sari\t: It\u2019s my boss. He said that I can have a day-offs earlier but \ntoday he revoked what he said. I was planning on going for a vacation on\n my day-offs with my family. I am extremely displeased about that.<br> Rangga\t: I\u2019m sorry to hear that.<br> Sari\t: Well, everyone has bad day but if we still consider it positively, everything is going to be alright<br> Rangga\t: Yeah, I think you\u2019re right<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "A = <span>why are you scared?<br>B = i&#039;am sorry. i spoil your diary.<br>A = what?? why did you do that?<br>B = i didn&#039;t purposely. sorry<br>A = wether the sorry can repair all?<br>B = OK. i will replace your diary, but iam sorry<br>A = it&#039;s up to you. <br></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}